Preliminary Inventory of the James Hayes papers
Hoover Institution Archives
James Hayes papers
1750-1998
93004
Hoover Institution Archives
11 manuscript boxes, 44 oversize boxes, 1 oversize scroll (32.2 linear feet)
Reports, minutes, correspondence, memoranda, contracts, maps, and printed matter, relating to various aspects of governmental administration of Hong Kong, and especially to regulation of labor. Includes scrolls of calligraphy by Ching dynasty scholar-officials of Kwangtung Province, China.
Hayes, James, 1930-
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1993.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical/Historical Note
British civil servant; deputy commissioner of labor, Hong Kong.
Scope and Content of Collection
Reports, minutes, correspondence, memoranda, contracts, maps, and printed matter, relating to various aspects of governmental administration of Hong Kong, and especially to regulation of labor. Includes scrolls of calligraphy by Ching dynasty scholar-officials of Kwangtung Province, China.
Calligraphy, Chinese.; China--Civilization.; China--History--Quing dynasty, 1644-1912.; Great Britain--Colonies.; Guangdong Sheng (China)--History.; Hong Kong (China); Hong Kong (China)--Politics and government.; Labor policy--China--Hong Kong.
- Calligraphy scrolls by Ching dynasty scholar-officials of Kwangtung Province, China (Box 1)
  - Zhang Weibing (three scrolls), undated (Box 1 and 5)
  - Chen Gongyin, undated (Box 1)
  - Feng Mingchang, undated (Box 1)
  - Huang Peifang, undated (Box 1)
  - Wu Rongguang, undated (Box 1)
  - Ma Haiwei, undated (Box 2)
  - Luo Shusheng (two scrolls), undated (Box 2)
  - Chen Han (four scrolls), undated (Box 2)
  - Liang Yaoshu (two scrolls), undated (Box 3)
  - Luo Wenzhong (two scrolls), undated (Box 3)
  - Li Erqiao, undated (Box 3)
  - Huang Huaisen (three scrolls), undated (Box 3 and 8)
  - Li Wentian (four scrolls), undated (Box 3 and 7)
  - Unidentified (two scrolls), undated (Box 4)
  - Dai Hongli (two scrolls), undated (Box 4)
  - Chen Ziqing (two scrolls), undated (Box 4)
  - Tan Zongqing (two scrolls), undated (Box 4)
  - Unidentified (two scrolls), 1990 (Box 4)
  - Deng Chengbei (two scrolls), undated (Box 4)
  - Bao Jun (six scrolls), undated (Box 5)
  - Long Yuanchuan (two scrollls), undated (Box 5)
  - Huang Danshu (three scrolls), undated (Box 5)
  - Zhu Ciqi (two scrolls), undated (Box 6)
  - Su Yaokui, undated (Box 6)
  - Huang Zigao (two scrolls), undated (Box 6)
  - Zeng Wangyan (three scrolls), undated (Box 6 and 8)
  - Liu Guangyan (two scrolls), undated (Box 6)
  - Chen Botao (three scrolls), undated (Box 6)
  - Unidentified (two scrolls), undated (Box 6)
  - Gao Yaopeng (two scrolls), undated (Box 6)
  - Feng Youyi (four scrolls), undated (Box 7)
  - Song Xiang (two scrolls), undated (Box 7)
  - Huang Yuezhi (two scrolls), undated (Box 7)
  - Gui Yao, undated (Box 8)
  - Unidentified (two scrolls), undated (Box 8)
  - Peng Dailai (four scrolls), undated (Box 8)
- Historical photographs of Hong Kong, 1994 (Box 8)
- Hong Kong public administration files, 1946-1982 (Box 9)
  - General labor reports and brief, 1946-1987 (Box-folder 9:1)
  - "Tsuen Wan New Town Development Plan" and "Brief on Minimum Wage Legislation in Hong Kong,", 1976 (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Ta Tit Street, Kwloon City land, 1979 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - City Monograph prepared for the Regional Congress of Local Authorities for Development of Human Settlements in Asia and the Pacific, 1982 (Box-folder 9:4)
  - Hong Kong Labor Committee, reports and brief, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9:5)
  - Public speeches of James Hayes, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9:6)
  - Development proposal of Tai Po district, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 9:7)
  - 1987 Nagoya congress materials (Box-folder 9:8)
  - General district administration circular, 1987 (Box-folder 9:9)
  - Passport of Wong Chu Pik, 1950 (Box-folder 9:10)
- Hong Kong land survey maps and leaseholder lists, undated (Box 10)
  - Map of seven villages, undated (Box 10)
  - Kowloon city survey maps (6 sheets), undated (Box 10)
  - Map of crown lands, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Leaseholder lists (two copies), undated (Box 10)
- Public speeches and meeting minutes, 1983-1995 (Box 11)
  - Labor Advisory Board Committee meeting minutes, 1983 (Box-folder 11:1)
  - District Management Committee meeting minutes, 1983 (Box-folder 11:2)
  - "The Changing Pattern of Employment in Hong Kong" a speech to the Retail Management Association and related conference papers, 1984 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Industrial Safety and Accident Prevention Committee of Labor Advisory Board meeting minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Registrar of Trade Unions Hong Kong, publicity unit materials, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 11:5)
  - "Where do we go from here? Trends in labor legislation" speech to the American Chamber of Commerce Employee Relations Committee, 1985 (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Contemporary Hong Kong clippings, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Restoration of the Ancient Gates of Kan Tin, New Territories materials, 1925 (Box-folder 11:8)
  - "Teaching Local Geography" materials, 1951 (Box-folder 11:9)
  - New Territories of Hong Kong notes, 1937 (Box-folder 11:10)
  - Intellectus: Bulletin of the Hong Kong Institute of Economic Science, 1991 (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Flag, badges, seals, and arms of Hong Kong, 1963 (Box-folder 11:12)
  - Campaign and tourism brochure, 1993 (Box-folder 11:13)
  - Volunteer: The Journal of the Royal Hong Kong Regiment, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 11:14)
- Tsuen Wan Files, 1930-1997 (Box 11-12)
  Includes village removal and land redevelopment materials.
  - Digest of instructions from the secretary of state for the colonies regarding disposal and tenure of land in the colony of Hong Kong, 1930 (Box-folder 11:15)
  - Crown lands resumption ordinance, 1960 (Box-folder 11:16)
  - Cheung Shan, clearance of squatter cultivators, 1976 (Box-folder 11:17)
  - List of re-sited villages, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 11:18)
  - Village removals, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 11:19)
  - Map of Tsuen Wan, New Territories, 1978 (Box-folder 12:1)
  - "Hong Kong Housing Annual Reports on Clearance Squatter Control and Redevelopment" extract, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Tsuen Wan information from Hong Kong University, geography department, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Tai Wang Ha village removal clearance, 1980 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Mass transit railway extension to Tsuen Wan, 1981 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Agenda and aid-memoire for meeting with Hoi Pa, 1981 (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Village removal situation reports, 1981 (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Village extention area and uses of small house policy to supplement village removal reports, 1981 (Box-folder 12:8)
  - Tsing Yi general development aid-memoire, 1981 (Box-folder 12:9)
  - Tsuen Wan redevelopment, newspaper and magazine clippings, 1982-1997 (Box-folder 12:10)
  - Hong Kong labor department correspondence, 1984 (Box-folder 12:11)
  - "Joint Declaration" white paper, 1984 (Box-folder 12:12)
  - City and New Territories administrative correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 12:13)
  - Academic journals and thesis, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 12:14)
  - "The New Town Experience Conference" correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 12:15)
  - "Representative Government in Hong Kong" white paper, 1994 (Box-folder 12:16)
  - Human Rights sub-committee, terms of reference, 1996 (Box-folder 12:17)
  - Notes for use in the District Land Offices, New Territories, undated (Box-folder 12:18)
  - Crown lease schedule extract, undated (Box-folder 12:19)
- Tsuen Wan materials on community building and town management materials, 1959-1991 (Box 12-13)
  - Visits to non-government associations, 1959-1978 (Box-folder 12:20)
  - New Territories and city administration memoranda, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 12:21)
  - Yeung UK Hawker Bazaar clearances, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Tsuen Wan papers and speeches, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Tsuan Wan sports and recreation projects, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Town management reports, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Tsuen Wan environmental control section report, 1981 (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Town management list, 1981 (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Community building, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 13:7)
  - "A History of Export Design in Hong Kong,", 1988 (Box-folder 13:8)
  - "The Heritage of Hong Kong,", 1992 (Box-folder 13:9)
  - "Administering the New Town of Hong Kong,", undated (Box-folder 13:10)
- District administration and regional planning materials, 1966-1993 (Box 14)
  - Local administration report by Colonial Secretariat, 1966 (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Regional Secretary of the New Territory files, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Articles about district administration, 1984, 1986 and 1987 (Box-folder 14:3)
  - Summary of results of an opinion poll, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 14:4)
  - District board administration files, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 14:5)
  - New Territory Rotary Club speech, 1985 (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Regional Secretary of New Territory, minutes of staff meetings, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 14:7)
  - Development proposals to the district board, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 14:8)
  - Improvements to living conditions in rural New Territory, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 14:9)
  - Governor's visit to Tuen Mun, 1986 (Box-folder 14:10)
  - Opinion survey on civic education, 1987 (Box-folder 14:11)
  - Quarterly statistics reports, 1987 (Box-folder 14:12)
  - Hong Kong city monograph for Nagoya Congress, 1987 (Box-folder 14:13)
  - Urban and new town development maps, 1993 (Box-folder 14:14)
  - New Territory land ordinance, 1895-1905 (Box-folder 14:15)
- Customary law files, 1895-1997 (Box 15)
  - Customary law in Tsuan Wan, 1966-1986 (Box-folder 15:1-3)
  - Customary law materials, 1986-1997 (Box-folder 15:4-7)
  - Correspondence about customary law, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 15:8)
  - Regional Secretary of the New Territory meetings with Senior Liaison Offices, 1987 (Box-folder 15:9)
  - Hong Kong customary laws review, 1987 (Box-folder 15:10)
  - Women's status and arranged marriage materials, 1980s (Box-folder 15:11)
  - Studies of Chinese customary laws, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 15:12)
  - Seminar schedules, requests for materials and visit memoranda, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 15:13)
  - New Territory succession, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 15:14)
  - Survey reports about systems in the New Territory, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 15:15)
  - "A Selection of Constitutional Documents Conventions and Treaties,", Undated (Box-folder 15:16)
  - "Chinese Law and Customs in Hong Kong" draft, 1997 (Box-folder 15:17)
- Government and Civic publications, 1858-1994 (Box 16-18)
  - "Hong Kong Police Magazine," four volumes, 1952-1957 (Box 16)
  - "Conservation of The Hong Kong Countryside,", April 1965 (Box 16)
  - "Conference on Development and Conservation of the Countryside,", 1969 (Box 16)
  - "Islands,", 1983 (Box 16)
  - "Land,", 1984 (Box 16)
  - "A Draft Agreement between the Government of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland and the Government of The People's Republic of China on the Future of Hong Kong,", 1984 (Box 16)
  - "Tsuen Wan,", 1987 (Box 16)
  - "Opinion," three volumes, 1987 (Box 16)
  - "Report of the Working Group on the New Territories Ordinance,", 1988 (Box 16)
  - "Sunday Morning Post: Hong Kong Annual Review," three volumes, 1987-1989 (Box 16)
  - "Hong Kong the Facts,", 1988-1991 (Box 16)
  - "The Week in Hong Kong,", 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - "Intellectus: Bulletin of the Hong Kong Institute of Economic Science" two volumes, 1991 (Box 16)
  - "The Future of Hong Kong's Past,", 1991 (Box 16)
  - "The Hong Kong Institute of Architects Newsletter,", 1991 (Box 16)
  - "Report of the Special Committee on Compensation and Betterment," two booklets, 1992 (Box 16)
  - "15 Years Public Works,", 1994 (Box 16)
  - "Green Paper: A Pattern of District Administration in Hong Kong,", Jun.1980 (Box 17)
  - "White Paper: District Administration in Hong Kong,", 1981 (Box 17)
  - "A Brief on the International Labour Organization,", 1983 (Box 17)
  - "Green Paper: The Further Development of Representative Government in Hong Kong," three booklets, 1984 (Box 17)
  - "Visitor Profile Report,", 1984 (Box 17)
  - "Report of the Antiquities Advisory Board," three booklets, 1982-1985 (Box 17)
  - "New Territory Development Plans," seven leaflets, 1985 (Box 17)
  - "Sha Tin In Figures,", 1985 (Box 17)
  - "1997 and After: Will Hong Kong Survive?", 1985 (Box 17)
  - "Hong Kong's New Towns: Tsuen Wan,", 1985 (Box 17)
  - "Planning for Growth,", 1985 (Box 17)
  - "Tao Mind,", 1985 (Box 17)
  - "Hong Kong Taoist Association Bulletin,", 1985 (Box 17)
  - "Hong Kong Taoist Association Joint-School Graduation Ceremony,", 1986 (Box 17)
  - "Briefing Notes on the Implementation of the Sino-British Joint Declaration,", 1986 (Box 17)
  - "Quarterly Statistical Report,", 1987 (Box 17)
  - "Land-use and Land-use Change in the Reclaimed Coastal Areas of Deep Bay,", 1987 (Box 17)
  - "Public Response to Green Paper: The 1987 Review of Developments in Representative Government," (Box 17)
  - "A Brief on the International Labour Organization,", 1988 (Box 17)
  - "Development Management Appraisal Report,", 1988 (Box 17)
  - "The Week in Hong Kong,", 1989-1991 (Box 17)
  - "Sai Kung and Clear Water Bay: General Information and Directory,", 1989 (Box 17)
  - "Commentary on the Draft Hong Kong Bill of Rights Ordinance,", 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Hong Kong, Inc." four volumes, 1990 (Box 17)
  - "Social Welfare,", 1992 (Box 17)
  - "New Town Experience Joint Conference,", 1993 (Box 17)
  - "The Hong Kong Monthly Magazine,", 1858 (Box 18)
  - "A Summary Memorandum on the Southern District of the New Territories,", 1955 (Box 18)
  - "Tai Po Dragon Boat Race,", 1985 (Box 18)
  - Hong Kong Buddhist Association printed materials, 1985 (Box 18)
  - "A Comparison of the Economic and Social Situation of Hong Kong With Nine Selected Economies,", 1986 (Box 18)
  - "Tsuen Wan" by the Territory Development Department, 1986 (Box 18)
  - "A Concise Guide to the Employment Ordinance,", 1987 (Box 18)
  - "Sai Kung" by the Territory Development Department, 1988 (Box 18)
  - "Junk Bay" by the Territory Development Department, 1988 (Box 18)
  - "Hong Kong After Tiananmen Square, A Counter-Cyclical View,", 1990 (Box 18)
  - "Green Paper: On Equal Opportunities for Women and Men,", 1991 (Box 18)
  - "Museum Bulletin,", 1987-1992 (Box 18)
- I. Mortgage contracts (Box 19-20)
  Arrangement note
  Arranged in groups, then by owner
  - 1. Mortgage of farmland (Box 19)
    - Zhan Yuan, 1813 (Folder 19: 1)
    - Gui Zhangzu, 1830 (Folder 19: 2)
    - Lu Xinqiu, 1851 (Folder 19: 3)
    - Yang Changyan, etc., 1858 (Folder 19: 4)
    - Tang - Lin, Tang Jielun, Tang Jiexiang, 1862 (Folder 19: 5)
    - Yang Shenxin, 1867 (Folder 19: 6)
    - Lu Xinguang, 1870 (Folder 19: 7)
    - Lu Xinguang, 1874 (Folder 19: 8)
    - Lu Xinguang, 1874 (Folder 19: 9)
    - Yi Guang, 1876 (Folder 19: 10)
    - Jiang Weizheng, 1885 (Folder 19: 11)
    - Lin Heji, 1885 (Folder 19: 12)
    - Ouyang Wang, 1888 (Folder 19: 13)
    - Liang Qiqi, 1893 (Folder 19: 14)
    - Hui Cheng, 1895 (Folder 19: 15)
    - Tang Chunshe, Peixing's mother - Kuang, 1896 (Folder 19: 16)
    - Xie Yangzhi, 1896 (Folder 19: 17)
    - Huang Shiyue, 1898 (Folder 19: 18)
    - Ya Zhi, 1898 (Folder 19: 19)
    - Feng Zhaoxiang shen, 1902 (Folder 19: 20)
    - Xie Jiekai, 1906 (Folder 19: 21)
    - Tang Zhen, 1908 (Folder 19: 22)
    - Zhong ?, 1908 (Folder 19: 23)
    - Zhong Lun, 1910 (Folder 19: 24)
    - Lu Chuangbiao, 1911 (Folder 19: 25)
    - Huang Wenjun, 1914 (Folder 19: 26)
    - Li Shiqin, 1915 (Folder 19: 27)
    - Liu Guo, Liu Zhihuai, 1915 (Folder 19: 28)
    - Chang Rui, 1916 (Folder 19: 29)
    - Pan Leshou, 1916 (Folder 19: 30)
    - Niang Sheng, 1917 (Folder 19: 31)
    - Wang Gouxiao, 1919 (Folder 19: 32)
    - Bao Quanshen, 1922 (Folder 19: 33)
    - Sister-in-law of Liangyin - Chen, 1923 (Folder 19: 34)
    - Liao Kezhi, 1924 (Folder 19: 35)
    - Chen Baoqi, 1936 (Folder 19: 36)
    - Huang Yuanfen, 1936 (Folder 19: 37)
    - Jiang Lugui, 1941 (Folder 19: 38)
    - Liao Shuxin, 1942 (Folder 19: 39)
    - Zhang Haijin, 1942 (Folder 19: 40)
    - Dao Zhi, 1943 (Folder 19: 41)
    - Jiang Zhongrong, 1943 (Folder 19: 42)
    - Wu Manzhen, 1943 (Folder 19: 43)
  - 2. Mortgage of land or pond (Box 20)
    - Lu Xingming (Folder 20: 1)
    - Liang Pinqian, etc. (Folder 20: 2)
    - Wu Riyun (Folder 20: 3)
    - Huang Yongying (Folder 20: 4)
    - Xie Chunzhong, Xie Chunzhong (Folder 20: 5)
    - Cheng, Qihui (Folder 20: 6)
    - Huang Zhaojun, Huang Zhaoduan (Folder 20: 7)
    - Huang Jizhen, Huang Xianlin (Folder 20: 8)
    - Huang Shiqiang (Folder 20: 9)
    - Tan Runan (Folder 20: 10)
  - 3. Mortgage of house or shop (Box 20)
    - Yang Liangzhi, Yang Quanzhi (Folder 20: 11)
    - Jiang Zhaochun, Jiang Songkuan (Folder 20: 12)
    - Zhang-Wu (Folder 20: 13)
    - Liang Rongxi (Folder 20: 14)
    - He Pingguang (Folder 20: 15)
    - Cao Chengdetang (Folder 20: 16)
    - Liu Yichang (Folder 20: 17)
    - Yang Guozhi (Folder 20: 18)
    - Liang Sungui (Folder 20: 19)
    - Fang-Liu (Folder 20: 20)
    - Lin Youdu (Folder 20: 21)
    - Li Daosheng (Folder 20: 22)
    - Dong Qingtang (Folder 20: 23)
    - Zheng Mianliang (Folder 20: 24)
    - Chen-Zhao (Folder 20: 25)
  - 4. Mortgage of orchard (Box 20)
    - Lin Niang'en (Folder 20: 26)
    - Ya An (Folder 20: 27)
    - Jia Gu (Folder 20: 28)
    - Lin Jiahong (Folder 20: 29)
    - Liu Wenxi (Folder 20: 30)
  - 5. Mortgage of share or deed (Box 20)
    - Jiang Xianchang (Folder 20: 31)
    - Tang Chun She, Brothers of Jiangbing ? (Folder 20: 32)
- II. Will or distribution of estate deed (Box 21)
  Arranged by bequeather
  - Huang Yanzong (Folder 21: 1)
  - Zhao Xintang (Folder 21: 2)
  - Zhang Han (Folder 21: 3)
  - Zhang Hong (Folder 21: 4)
  - Jiang Xiangchang, Jiang Xiantai (Folder 21: 5)
  - Yang Guozhi, etc. (Folder 21: 6)
  - Chen Chengbang (Folder 21: 7)
  - Zheng Kuirong (Folder 21: 8)
  - Da Ting (Folder 21: 9)
  - Shaochang - Li (Folder 21: 10)
  - Huang Qijun, Huang Shiqiang (Folder 21: 11)
  - parents of Chen and Liu (Folder 21: 12)
  - Da Ting (Folder 21: 13)
- III. Contract of betrothal, Gu Shufei, Huang Jieying (Folder 21: 14)
- IV. Share receipts or partnership contracts (Box 21)
  Arranged by owners
  - Feng Jingben tang, Xie Shenyuan Tang (Folder 21: 15)
  - Dong Qing (Folder 21: 16)
  - Fa (Folder 21: 17)
    Scope and Contents note
    Certificate in envelope
  - He Baoshan (Folder 21: 18)
  - Huang Yuqing (Folder 21: 19)
    Envelope only. Certificate No. 2 Missing
  - Huang Xiufu (Folder 21: 20)
- V. Loan contract (Box 21)
  Arranged by borrower
  - Qi Xiang (Folder 22: 1)
  - Ru Fang (Folder 22: 2)
  - Ouyang Sun, Ouyang Lixiang (Folder 22: 3)
  - Chen Laijiu (Folder 22: 4)
  - Ouyang Gu (Folder 22: 5)
  - Huang Yingliang (Folder 22: 6)
  - Wu Jiniang (Folder 22: 7)
  - Chen Shugao (Folder 22: 8)
  - Chen Yihui (Folder 22: 9)
  - Chen Jintang (Folder 22: 10)
- VI. Adoption or sale of girl contract (Box 22)
  - 1. Adoption or sale of daughter (Box 22)
    Arranged by parents
    - Xie bing (Folder 22: 12)
    - Zhou xing, Zhou (Folder 22: 13)
    - Li ruzhen, Huang Huanjin (Folder 22: 14)
  - 2. Sale of maid, Mai Yandi (Folder 22: 15)
- VII. Business transaction contracts (Box 23-44)
  - 1. Sale of farmland (Box 23-38)
    Arranged by owner
    - Yang Deli, etc. (Folder 23: 1)
    - Zheng Yaozhang, etc. (Folder 23: 2)
    - Li Yuntong (Folder 23: 3)
    - Zhi Dajing (Folder 23: 4)
    - Zhang Zilin (Folder 23: 5)
    - Su Yanhou, etc. (Folder 23: 6)
    - Tang Gaobiao (Folder 23: 7)
    - Ye Tiyu, etc. (Folder 23: 8)
    - He Xingbei, etc. (Folder 23: 9)
    - Li Mingzhou, etc. (Folder 23: 10)
    - Lin Yuanwei (Folder 23: 11)
    - Tan Gao, Tan Yueming (Folder 23: 12)
    - Liao Shuding (Folder 23: 13)
    - Liao Zhuofan, etc. (Folder 23: 14)
    - Hu Peisen, etc. (Folder 23: 15)
    - Lin Tingxian (Folder 23: 16)
    - Liang Chengfang, etc. (Folder 23: 17)
    - Gao Xingzu (Folder 23: 18)
    - Liang Chaoyuan, etc. (Folder 23: 19)
    - Zhang Ade, etc. (Folder 23: 20)
    - Zhu Chongzhang, etc. (Folder 23: 21)
    - Ouyang Baoru (Folder 23: 22)
    - Zhang ?? (Folder 23: 23)
    - Li Guoshao (Folder 24: 1)
    - Li Guowei, etc. (Folder 24: 2)
    - Li Yingsong (Folder 24: 3)
    - Hu Xinzong (Folder 24: 4)
    - Li-Huang,etc. (Folder 24: 5)
    - Lu Ruixian (Folder 24: 6)
    - Zhang Dianyang (Folder 24: 7)
    - Luo Zhichang (Folder 24: 8)
    - Luo Dakui (Folder 24: 9)
    - Luo Zhulin (Folder 24: 10)
    - Luo Maochang (Folder 24: 11)
    - Luo Nengchang (Folder 24: 12)
    - Mo Shixian, 1913 (Folder 24: 13)
    - Shao Guzu, etc. (Folder 24: 14)
    - Ye Heyi, etc. (Folder 24: 15)
    - Chen Xiji (Folder 24: 16)
    - Liang Yongnian (Folder 24: 17)
    - Mo Shixian, 1913 (Folder 24: 18)
    - Xiao Jinguang (Folder 24: 19)
    - Zheng Shenhe & Mother Li (Folder 24: 20)
    - Liang Juxian, 1914 (Folder 24: 21)
    - Liang Yongnian, 1914 (Folder 24: 22)
    - Xu Haizhen (Folder 24: 23)
    - Pan Runan, etc. (Folder 24: 24)
    - Wen Yifu (Folder 24: 25)
    - He Hecong (Folder 24: 26)
    - Zheng Jieyuan (Folder 24: 27)
    - Yang Renxian (Folder 24: 28)
    - Yang Rengen (Folder 24: 29)
    - Xie Shunkai (Folder 25: 1)
    - Lu Zhixian (Folder 25: 2)
    - Li Wenhui (Folder 25: 3)
    - He Changwen (Folder 25: 4)
    - He Changcong (Folder 25: 5)
    - He Dabang (Folder 25: 6)
    - Li Kebin, etc. (Folder 25: 7)
    - Liang Hongmei (Folder 25: 8)
    - Zhuang Shangqiao (Folder 25: 9)
    - Dong Guangong, etc. (Folder 25: 10)
    - Li Yingwen, etc. (Folder 25: 11)
    - Huang Jianyuan (Folder 25: 12)
    - Liang Yongzhao, 1912 (Folder 25: 13)
    - Ruan Yangxian (Folder 25: 14)
    - Liang Yuwen, 1914 (Folder 25: 15)
    - Bao Renjia, 1912 (Folder 26: 1)
    - Ruan Jinglong, 1912 (Folder 26: 2)
    - Brothers of Wu? (Folder 26: 3)
    - Luo Xianfang (Folder 26: 4)
    - Huang Maoczhao, etc. (Folder 26: 5)
    - Su Jingyou (Folder 26: 6)
    - Deng Chonghua (Folder 26: 7)
    - Fang ? Ming (Folder 26: 8)
    - Huang Gongfang (Folder 26: 9)
    - Huang Shenghua (Folder 26: 10)
    - Yang Yuchuan (Folder 26: 11)
    - Chen Jin, etc. (Folder 26: 12)
    - Xie Liangmo (Folder 26: 13)
    - Zeng Yawu, Zhong YaMao, etc (Folder 26: 14)
    - Chen Yuhua, etc. (Folder 26: 15)
    - Zhong Yaxiang, Zhong Yegeng, etc. (Folder 26: 16)
    - Feng Yuxiong (Folder 26: 17)
    - Huang Yingshi (Folder 26: 18)
    - Shi Yuchu (Folder 26: 19)
    - Wu Chaorong, 1912 (Folder 26: 20)
    - Hu Songshou (Folder 26: 21)
    - Zhou Pinnan (Folder 26: 22)
    - Yang Shengke (Folder 27: 1)
    - Zheng Jialan, 1912 (Folder 27: 2)
    - Liang Yayou (Folder 27: 3)
    - Wu Deyou (Folder 27: 4)
    - Yan Qiaoying (Folder 27: 5)
    - Cai Zhidian (Folder 27: 6)
    - Hu Xiao (Folder 27: 7)
    - Liang Changxi, etc., 1914 (Folder 27: 8)
    - Luo Zhuguo, 1913 (Folder 27: 9)
    - Wei Donglang (Folder 27: 10)
    - Yang Lizhi, etc. (Folder 27: 11)
    - Liang Qishi (Folder 27: 12)
    - Wei Donglang (Folder 27: 13)
    - Liang (Folder 27: 14)
    - Sun Fuzu (Folder 27: 15)